pushwoosh.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy - Pushwoosh

PUSHWOOSH PRIVACY POLICY

Arello Mobile provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of [www.pushwoosh.com](http://www.pushwoosh.com/) (the “Website”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Website. Our Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

YOU ARE HEREBY ADVISED THAT YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, ANY APPLICABLE CURRENT AND PRIOR VERSIONS, AND ANY AMENDMENTS THERETO.

Information Collection: The Personally Identifiable Information We Collect

In the course of using the Website, you may provide us with personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, and information on your use of and activities at the Website that may be connected with you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information that we collect may include, but is not limited to, your name and email address. When you visit the Website, our servers automatically record information that your browser or device sends whenever you active on the website, this information may include personal information, accounts’ data for sending notifications, notifications’ messages and their rich content. Like many websites, we may also use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Website. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Website or all functionality of our services.

When you register applications (“App(s)”) to the Website, we may also record certain statistics information related thereto, such as the number registered devices. The number of notifications you have send is also saved for statistics data. All application sensitive information remains your property and shall not be part of the Personal Information. We make no claim to ownership of any Apps unless created and uploaded by us.

How We Use Personal Information

Personal Information is or may be used for the following purposes: (i) to provide and improve the Website, services, features and content, (ii) to administer your use of the Website, (iii) to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate the Website, (iv) to better understand your needs and interests, (v) to fulfill requests you may make, (vi) to personalize your experience, (vii) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements, and (viii) to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on services and products offered by us or third parties. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive any such communications, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of the communications sent to you.

We use information we obtain by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies) for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of the Website and our services, for the Website’s technical administration, to increase the Website’s functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to your needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and to verify that visitors to the Website meet the criteria required to process their notifications.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will display your Personal Information in your profile page on the Website according to the preferences you set in your account. Your personal information will be displayed on opening your profile preferences which are available only for you as long as you are the only person who knows login and password for your account. We recommend you to guard your login and password information. You can review and revise your profile information at any time.

Service Providers, Business Partners and Others. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our service, to provide the service on our behalf, to perform Website-related services (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Website’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how the Website and service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. Arello Mobile cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Arello Mobile or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable.

Right to Reference. Unless you provide express written notice otherwise, Arello Mobile shall have the right to reference and refer to the usage of, and relationship with, you or your company, which may be determined by the domain used in your registered email account. No press releases shall be made without your written consent.

Business Transfers. Arello Mobile may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with or in anticipation of a corporate event, including a merger, acquisition, sale of stock, recapitalization, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

Changing or Deleting Your Information

You may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided in your registration or account profile by changing your “account settings.”

Security

Arello Mobile is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ reasonable measures and security designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. These measures including encrypting sensitive information using a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and storing information behind a firewall. However, Arello Mobile cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Transfer of Information

If you are not a resident of Russian Federation, you understand and agree that Arello Mobile stores and processes your information on computers located in Russian Federation, and by providing any data to Arello Mobile, you consent to the transfer of such information to Russian Federation and the application of the laws of Russian Federation.

Our Policy Toward Children

This Website is not directed to children under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@pushwoosh.com](mailto:privacy@pushwoosh.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@pushwoosh.com](mailto:privacy@pushwoosh.com).

Updated: June, 2011

This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time, with or without notice to you. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for any amendments or changes.

Pushwoosh https://www.pushwoosh.com/wp-content/themes/pushwoosh/img/logo.png support@pushwoosh.com
